Aizza Viera

CURRICULUM VITAE

<u>aizzakatrina@outlook.com</u> <u>aizzakatrina.com</u>

SUMMARY

A data analyst with a background in financial reporting, and experience in data/quantitative analysis. Strong knowledge of databases, information systems, and business processes with a track-record for adhering to deadlines. Demonstrated ability to explore, interpret, and extract value from data enabling effective strategic planning in business operations.

EDUCATION

Data Analytics Certificate. University of California, Berkeley. 2018 B.A. Economics, with Accounting concentration. California State University, East Bay. 2016

SKILLS

Data modeling and visualization. Regression analysis. Machine learning. Web scraping. Financial analysis and modeling. **Programming Languages**: SQL, Python, C++, R, Mongo, Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VBA **Software**: Advanced Excel (vlookups, nested functions, charts and graphs, pivot tables), Jupyter Notebook, Tableau, Mode Analytics, Looker, Power BI

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst. Coalition. San Francisco, CA. 2021-Present

Financial Operations Analyst. Jyve Corporation. San Francisco, CA. 2020–2021.

Financial Operations Consultant. Nabis. San Francisco, CA. 2019-2020.

Accounting Analyst. Origin House. Santa Rosa, CA. 2018-2019

Staff Accountant. The RealReal Inc. San Francisco, CA. 2015–2018

Accountant. Stay Winning Boutique. Fremont, CA. 2014-2015

Bookkeeper. McCaulous Inc. Napa, CA. 2012

Student Assistant. Department of Human Development and Women's Studies. California State University, East Bay. 2012

COMMUNITY SERVICE

Accounting Volunteer. Loved Twice. Oakland, CA. 2011–2013